Guide to the Tri-State Conference on Manufacturing Records, 1978-1993 AIS.1993.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Working File (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, Document Process, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, Steel (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Document Financing, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Institute for American Values, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Wendy Patton, Application for Tri-State Economic Researcher Position (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Cleveland, Chase Brass, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Cleveland, RIC, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Cleveland, Steel Study (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, Early Warning Signals Network (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Plant Shutdowns (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program and General Electric (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, Industrial Inventory Research, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, Jim Benn's Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, Federation for Industrial Retention (Box 27, Folder 31)
- House Bill 1400, An Act Creating the Pennsylvania Industrial Development Finance Corporation, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 32-47)
- Micha Project and House Bill 1400, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- Legislative Resources and Campaign Materials (Box 27, Folder 49)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Financing, Industrial Capital Fund, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Caravan, ICF Presentation to Groups (Box 27, Folder 51)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Caravan, Brochure Material (Box 27, Folder 52)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Pennsylvania, Caravan Project, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 53)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Caravan, Farmer Organizations, 1985-1987 (Box 27, Folder 54)
- Action Housing Annual Report, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 55)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Caravan, Legislators Packet (Box 27, Folder 56)
- House Bill 1400, PA Economic Development Partnership, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 57)
- Industrial Capital Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 58)
- Eastern Industrial Valleys Community of Faith (Box 27, Folder 59-64)
- Newsletter Mailing List (Box 27, Folder 65)
- PERF Package (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Pennsylvania Renaissance through Educational Preparedness and Retraining Efforts Package (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1980s (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
- Reports, Proposals, Resolutions and Clippings regarding Plant Closures and the Economy (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Steel Valley Authority v. Union Switch and Signal (Box 28, Folder 6)
- An Interstate River Valley in Economic Transition: The Monongahela River Valley Summit Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Directory of Iron and Steel Works of the United States and Canada, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Plant Closures Project, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Omnibus: A Planning Newspaper for Southwestern Pennsylvania, April 1986 and January 1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Reports and Papers (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Organizations (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Steel Valley Authority, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Tri-State Conference on Steel (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Regional Economic Models, Inc. (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Plant Closures (Box 28, Folder 17)
- WDVE and John Cafferty & the Beaver Brown Band Concert for Tri-State (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Transnational Corporations and the Internationalization of Production: A Global Perspective on the US Steel Industry in Crisis by Cynthia Deitch, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Shutdown at GATX and the Railcar Industry of Northwest Indiana: A Plant Closing Evaluation Report by Midwest Center for Labor Research, 1984 (Box 28, Item 1)
- Dorothy 6: Financial Feasibility of Reopening the Duquesne Works by Lazard Freres & Co., 1986 (Box 28, Item 2)
- Building Economic Alternatives by Co-Op America, 1987 (Box 28, Item 3)
- Massachusetts High Tech: The Promise and the Reality, 1984 (Box 28, Item 4)
- UAW Research Bulletin, 1985 (Box 28, Item 5)
- Relative Profitability of the US and Japanese Steel Industries by Kiyoshi Kawahito, 1984 (Box 28, Item 6)
- State Venture Capital Initiatives by Greg Bettger, 1986 (Box 28, Item 7)
- Business Assistance Programs in Washington State, 1986 (Box 28, Item 8)
- Employee Ownership: Lessons Learned by William Foote Whyte, 1984 (Box 28, Item 9)
- Capital Strategies for Labor by Malon Wilkus, 1985 (Box 28, Item 10)
- Letters of Support regarding Tri-State, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- International Economic Conversion Conference, June 22-24, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Resolutions and Reports of US Steel Stockholder Meetings, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Confernece of Major Superiors of Men Tour, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 4-5)
- Chicago Department of Economic Development Documents regarding Steel Companies, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Tri-State News Clippings, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 7-8)
- Plan to Revitalize Mon Valley Steelmaking, Activities, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- "Rebuild Steel" Plan Summary and Responses, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Newsletters (Box 29, Folder 11-12)
- Tri-State Meetings and Agenda, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Tri-State Regional Reindustrialization Project (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Tri State, Steel Valley Authority (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Tri-State, American Standard and Switch & Brake (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Pittsburgh Economy, Manufacturing (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Film Showings of "The Business of America", 1984 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Denominational Ministry Strategy, Network to Save the Mon/Ohio Valley, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Tri-State Activities, 1979-1984 (Box 29, Folder 20-24)
- Steel Valley Town Meeting, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Forward: Journal of Socialist Thought, January 1987 (Box 29, Item 1)
- Partners in Progress: The Pennsylvania MILRITE Council Three Year Report (Box 29, Item 2)
- UAW Research Bulletin, October 1985 (Box 29, Item 3)
- IECON Newsletter by the Interreligious Economic Crisis Organizing Network, 1985 (Box 29, Item 4)
- Environmental Action, 1985 (Box 29, Item 5)
- Tri-State, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Pamphlet Master Copies (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Letters of Introduction to Tri-State (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Press (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Politicians (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Mon Valley Expressway (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Reports (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Papers (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Tri-State, Duquesne Works and Dorothy Six (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Tri-State, Pennsylvania Industrial Capital Fund (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Drafts of Brochures (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Jones & Laughlin Steel Communications, 1981-1983 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Financial Management in Public Organizations by Alan Walter Steiss, 1989 (Box 30, Item 1)
- Financial and Strategic Management for Nonprofit Organizations by J. Bryce Harrington, 1987 (Box 30, Item 2)
- Organizational Decline and Cutback Management by Charles H. Levine, 1978 (Box 30, Item 3)
- Managing a Nonprofit from an Accounting Perspective, 1988 (Box 30, Item 4)
- The Nonprofit Sector and the New Federal Budget by Alan J. Abramson and Lester M. Salamon (Box 30, Item 5)
- Review of the Steel Industry Plan by the Australian Steel industry Authority, 1988 (Box 30, Item 6)
- Steelabor, April 1986 and February 1989 (Box 30, Item 7-8)
- Feasibility Study of the Duquesne Works' Blast and Basic Oxygen Furnaces for United Steeworkers of America, Preliminary and Final Reports, 1985 (Box 30, Item 9-10)
- Dorothy 6: Financial Feasibility of Reopening the Duquesne Works by Lazard Freres & Co., 1986 (Box 30, Item 11)
- Managing by the University of Pittsburgh School of Business, 1979 (Box 30, Item 12)
- Latin American Perspectives, 1984 (Box 30, Item 13)
- Interim Report, Diocesan Task Force on Unemployment (Box 30, Item 14)
- The Dilemas of Export-Led Industrialization: South Korea and the World Economy by S.K. Cho, 1985 (Box 30, Item 15)
- Autonomous Development and the Restructuring of the World Capitalist System: A Study of the South Korean and the US Metal Working Industries (Box 30, Item 16)
- An Integrated Theory of the Economic Long Wave by John D. Sterman, 1985 (Box 30, Item 17)
- The Struggle for Democracy in South Korea in the 1980s and the Rise of Anti-Americanism by Tim Shorrock (Box 30, Item 18)
- Business Week, 1985 (Box 30, Item 19)
- Fundraising for Social Change, 1985 (Box 30, Item 20)
- Clippings and Newsletters (Box 31, Folder 1)
- The Nonprofit Sector: A Research Handbook by Walter W. Powell, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- American Wealthy and the Future of Foundations, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Tri-State Information (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Steel Valley Authority and Duquesne (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Taxes and Assessment (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Mailing Lists (Box 31, Item 1)
- Student Packet, PIA 224 Management of Non-Profit Organizations (Box 31, Item 2)
- Save Switch and Brake Meeting Posters (Box 31, Item 3)
- Benefit Concert Flyer Master Copies (Box 31, Item 4)
- Posters for MAGLEV Project Town Meetings, 1990 (Box 31, Item 5)
- Audio from Meetings (Box 32, Cassette 1-8)
- A Broader Industrial Plan, October 29, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Tri-State News Releases regarding a Plan to Save Mon Valley Steel, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Tri-State Meeting Attendance, October 29, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Products and Markets Meeting, October 29, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Interviews and Conferences (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Attendee List and Transcript of "Organization of Production and Shop Floor Democracy" Meeting, October 29, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Financing an Authority Meeting, October 29, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Tri-State Steel Revitalization Plan, October 29, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Organization of Authority Meeting, October 29, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Steel Valley Authority (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Residents' Committee Stationary and Address Labels (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Tri-State Press Releases (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Press Clippings (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Statements of Support, US Steel Responses (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Local Government Officials, 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Gate Action, Phone Tree (Box 32, Folder 16)
- "What Dorothy Means to Me" Poster Contest (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Residents' Committee Petition Campaign (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Duquesne Works Maps (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Investment (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Pamphlets and Fliers (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Press Clippings, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Feasibility Studies regarding Duquesne Works (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Phelan: Relay Spinoff Proposal (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Duquesne Area Clergy Association, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Contact Lists, Duquesne (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Residents' Committee (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Domadar Prabhu Scheme to Restart Duquesne Works as Mini-Mill, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Furnace Winterization Fund, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Records regarding the Movement to save the LTV Aliquippa Works (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Newspaper Clippings, June-October 1988 (Box 32, Folder 32-36)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 1-6)
- Occupational Forecasts for the Pittsburgh Region by Edward Malloy and Chinn-Ping Fan, 1987 (Box 33, Item 1)
- City of Pittsburgh Six Year Development Program, 1991-1996 (Box 33, Item 2)
- The St. Joe Flame Reactor EAF Dust Treatment Process (Box 33, Item 3)
- Plasma Process Treatment of Stainless Steelmaking Furnace Dusts, 1987 (Box 33, Item 4)
- Metal Recovery from Oxidic Waste Using Plasma Technology by Hans G. Herlitz and Peter Baumann, 1987 (Box 33, Item 5)
- ZIA Technology, Inc., People Behind the Company (Box 33, Item 6)
- Steelmaking Electric Arc Furnace Dust Treatment with Elkem's Multi-Purpose Electric Furnace (Box 33, Item 7)
- Engineering and Costs of Davy McKee Hi-Plas Process for Metals Recovery from EAF Dusts by D. Naden, 1987 (Box 33, Item 8)
- Electric Arc Furnace Dust: Disposal, Recycle and Recovery, 1985 (Box 33, Item 9)
- Development of a Metal-Oxide Flash Smelting Reactor by J.F. Pusateri (Box 33, Item 10)
- Plasma Process Treatment of Stainless Steelmaking Furnace Dust, 1987 (Box 33, Item 11)
- Pre-Feasibility Study Potential Employee Buy-Out of Gateway Mine Preosperity, Pennsylvania, 1990 (Box 33, Item 12)
- United Steelworkers of America Officers' Report, 1988 (Box 33, Item 13)
- Plant Closing: Advance Notice and Rapid Response (Box 33, Item 14)
- Pennsylvania Right to Know and Sara Title III Compliance Materials for Employers, 1989 (Box 33, Item 15)
- Tri-State Membership Cards (Box 34, Item 1)
- Tri-State Committee Reports, 1988 (Box 34, Item 2)
- Worker Co-operative/Owned Companies (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Burlington Local Development Corp. (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Information from Battelle, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- US Steel and Steel Valley Authority, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence and Reports (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Financial Papers (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Contact Lists (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Newsletters (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Crossroads for America: Choosing a Better Future for American Industry and the American People (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Revitalization Program for the Mon Valley Area by Dick Thornburg (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Basic Steel Industry Conference, USWA Ratification Study Task Force (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Pittsburgh International Engineering, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 13)
- State of the Region for Western PA., Ohio & West Virginia by Regional Research, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- The Effect on Steel Demand of Increased Expenditures for Public Infrastructure, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Partial Shutdown of Diamond Tool: Analysis, Outlook and Options for Public Intervention, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- America's Steel Industry: A Time to Act, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- The Federal Roll in State Industrial Development Programs, 1984 (Box 35, Item 1)
- Report to the Allegheny County Board of Commissioners for the Economic Revitalization of the Monongahela, Youghiogheny, and Turtle Creek Valleys, 1987 (Box 35, Item 2)
- Project Report: Steel Retention Study by Arthur D. Little, Inc., 1988 (Box 35, Item 3)
- Horsehead Resource Development Company (Box 35, Item 4)
- Engineering and Costs of Davy McKee Hi-Plas Process for Metals Recovery from EAF Dusts by D. Naden, 1987 (Box 35, Item 5)
- Social Cost Analysis of Possible Shutdown of Cleveland LTV Works, 1987 (Box 35, Item 6)
- Reversing the Decline of the Steel Industry: In Theory and In Practice by Bruce P. Merenstein, 1986 (Box 35, Item 7)
- Participants, "Update Meeting on EAF Dust Activities" Sponsored by Center for Metals Production, June 18, 1987 (Box 35, Item 8)
- Steelabor Article on Duquesne Works, February 1985 (Box 35, Item 9)
- An Action Agenda for the Eighties: Turtle Creek Valley Development Plan (Box 35, Item 10)
- Worker Co-Ops, 1987 (Box 35, Item 11)
- Choosing a Legal Structure for a Democratically Operated Employee Owned Company: Cooperative or ESOP? (Box 35, Item 12)
- Pennsylvania Public Pension Funds for Economic Development by Robert W. Coy, Jr. (Box 35, Item 13)
- New Institutions for Regional Needs by Roger S. Ahlbrandt, Jr., 1985 (Box 35, Item 14)
- The Great Lakes Inland Waterway: Questions and Answers (Box 35, Item 15)
- Shutdown at GATX and the Railcar Industry of Northwest Indiana: A Plant Closing Evaluation Report by the Midwest Center for Labor Research, 1984 (Box 35, Item 16)
- Prospects for the Redevelopment of Industry in Southwestern Pennsylvania by Laura Ashley, 1986 (Box 35, Item 17)
- State Venture Capital Initiatives by Gary Bettger, 1986 (Box 35, Item 18)
- Changing Work: A Magazine About Liberating Worklife, 1985 (Box 35, Item 19)
- Summary Transcript of Proceedings, "The Future of Railroad Equipment Manufacturing in Northwest Indiana", November 10, 1984 (Box 35, Item 20)
- Interim Summary, Human Services Choices for Pennsylvanians, 1985 (Box 35, Item 21)
- For a National Industrial Policy That Will Create Jobs by Dr. Ann Markusen, May 20, 1988 (Box 35, Item 22)
- Starting With Real Worker-Management Cooperation: The Lessons of Steel in the Mon Valley by John Hoerr, May 20, 1988 (Box 35, Item 23)
- Lazard Freres & Co. (Box 35, Item 24)
- Lazard Freres & Co., Steel Industry and Employee Ownership Experience, 1988 (Box 35, Item 25)
- Directory of Workers Education by Workers Educational Local 189, 1982 (Box 35, Item 26)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance: New Ideas for an Old Program, 1987 (Box 35, Item 27)
- Plant Closing: Advance Notice and Rapid Response, 1986 (Box 35, Item 28)
- Tri-State Joe Magarac Award Dinner Programs, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Item 29-30)
- USWA John Dingell Pamphlet (Box 35, Item 31)
- Thinking About the Unthinkable: The Free Trade Fallacy by Bob Kuttner, 1983 (Box 35, Item 32)
- Constitution of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1982 (Box 35, Item 33)
- Plant Closing Checklist: A Guide to Best Practice (Box 35, Item 34)
- For Fair Trade in Steel: A Legislative Solution to the Crisis in American Steel (Box 35, Item 35)
- Labor's Testimonty Before the International Trade Commission on the 201 Petition Under the 1974 Trade Act, 1984 (Box 35, Item 36)
- Industrial Policy: Hearings Before the Subcommittee on Economic Stabilization, 1983 (Box 35, Item 37)
- "Steelworkers Do it With a Blast" Pin (Box 35, Item 38)
- "Save Dorothy 6" Pin (Box 35, Item 39)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Capital Strategies for Labor by Malon Wilkus of the Calvert Group, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Infrastructure Materials by the General Contractors of America (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Study on the Demand and Supply of Semifinished Steel Products in the United States, 1985 (Box 36, Item 1)
- Building on the Basics: The Final Report of the Mayor's Task Force on Steel and Southeast Chicago (Box 36, Item 2)
- Parish Action Handbook (Box 36, Item 3)
- Building Pittsburgh (Box 36, Item 4)
- Steel Retention Study (Box 36, Item 5)
- Reaganism: How Your Senators and Representatives Voted, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Item 6)
- Pension Funds and Economic Development: How Public and Private Pension Funds Can Contribute to the Pennsylvania Economy, 1983 (Box 36, Item 7)
- Industrial Capital Funding: An Examination of the Legislation and Systems Relating to Pennsylvania's House Bill 1400 by John Betzler, 1988 (Box 36, Item 8)
- "Recharge South Side" T-Shirt (Box 36, Item 9)
- Stand Up (Valley of Steel) by Joey G & Brick Alley Band Records, 1985 (Box 36, Item 10)
- Electric Furance Survey Cards (Box 36, Item 11-12)
- "Making South Side Steel" Public Service Announcement, 1988 (Box 36, Cassette 1)
- Buy Out (Box 36, Cassette 2)
- Steel Valley Authority, Tri-State Conference Workshop Tapes, October 29, 1983 (Box 36, Cassette 3-12)
- Regional Reindustrialization, Tri-State Conference Workshop Tapes, December 7, 1985 (Box 36, Cassette 13-24)
- "Save Dorothy 6 For Our Jobs, Families and Community" Banner (Box 37, Item 1)
- "End Unemployment TVA For Steel" Banner (Box 37, Item 2)
- Contact Cards (Box 37, Item 3)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
- Banking, 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Handwritten Notes (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Steel Valley Authority, 1985, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 38, Folder 7-8)
- Solidarity, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- 501 (c)(3) Monthly Letter (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Draft Resolutions (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Tri-State Conference on Steel (Box 38, Folder 12)
- LTV Steel (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Newsletters, Pamphlets and Posters (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Legislation (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Conferences (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Organizations (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Reports and Miscellaneous Papers (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Tri-State Deindustrialization Activities (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Fundraising (Box 38, Folder 20-21)
- Underinvestment and Economic Growth in the US: Construction/Investment Spending, An Engine of Economic Growth by Douglas M. Brown (Box 38, Item 1)
- America in Ruins - An Update: A Public Works Financing Strategy by Pat Choate (Box 38, Item 2)
- National Unemployed Network Update, May 1986 (Box 38, Item 3)
- House of Representatives Interviews regarding Pensions, 1987 (Box 38, Item 4)
- Crossroads for America: Choosing a Better Future for American Industry and the American People (Box 38, Item 5)
- The Church and the Economic Situation in Allegheny County: A Report to the Most Reverend P. Francis Murphy by Reverend William A. Au, 1985 (Box 38, Item 6)
- Interreligious Economic Crisis Organizing Network Steering Committee Resource Mailing, February 5, 1987 (Box 38, Item 7)
- The Mountain Messenger, 1984 (Box 38, Item 8)
- Milltowns in the Pittsburgh Region: Conditions and Prospects, 1983 (Box 38, Item 9)
- Economic Dislocation and Structural Unemployment: The Plight of America's Basic Industries, September 6, 1985 (Box 38, Item 10)
- Mid-Contract Reports by Mike Stout, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Item 11)
- Applying the Precedent of Walter Reuther's Defense Mobilization to the Mobilization of Unemployed Potential Today by Lyndon H. LaRouche, Jr. (Box 38, Item 12)
- The Grantsmanship Center Whole Nonprofit Catalog (Box 38, Item 13)
- Factory of the Future/Factory of the Past: Advanced Technology Comes to Lynn by Frank Emspak (Box 38, Item 14)
- Relationships between Participation, Personality and Work Attitudes (Box 38, Item 15)
- Regional Crisis-Community Crisis: An Overview of the Economy of the Great Lakes/Appalachian Region, 1984 (Box 38, Item 16)
- Confronting the Crisis: The Challenge for Labor, 1985 (Box 38, Item 17)
- Steelclips, January 1986 (Box 38, Item 18)
- Selection from Labor and Reindustrialization: Workers and Corporate Change by Donald Kennedy, 1984 (Box 38, Item 19)
- United States Steel Corporation Counter Annual Report by the Tri-State Conference on the Impact of Steel, 1980 (Box 38, Item 20)
- The Wage Investment and Union Role in Management Agreement at Eastern Air Lines (Box 38, Item 21)
- Toward a Working Ohio: Executive Summary (Box 38, Item 22)
- Just Economy: The Ecumenical Great Lakes/Appalachian Project on the Economic Crisis, October 1985 (Box 38, Item 23)
- Corporatism and Change: Austria, Switzerland and the Politics of Industry by Peter J. Katzenstein, 1985 (Box 38, Item 24)
- Annual Report on the Status of Transportation Planning for the Southwestern Pennsylvania Region by Southwestern Pennsylvania Regional Planning Commission, 1986 (Box 38, Item 25)
- Work Ethics: Newsletter of the Plant Closures Project, 1986 (Box 38, Item 26)
- Ploughshare, April-May 1987 (Box 38, Item 27)
- Detroit Free Press: Blue-Collar Casualties, August 31-September 5, 1986 (Box 38, Item 28)
- $$/The Non-Profit Management Reports (Box 38, Item 29)
- Communities Fight Industrial Abandonment: Naugatuck Valley Project and Steel Valley Authority Find New Strategies for the Rust Bowl by Jeremy Brecher (Box 38, Item 30)
- Economic Recovery: Doing a Poor Job for the Jobless Poor, July 5, 1985 (Box 38, Item 31)
- Employee Stock Ownership Plan Research (Box 39, Folder 1-23)
- Financing Concepts Research (Box 39, Folder 24-31)
- Financing Guidebooks: Industrial Cooperative Association (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Financing-Government: Community Development Block Grants (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Financing: Economic Development Administration (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Capitalization Schemes: US Small Business Administration (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Local Financing (Box 39, Folder 36-45)
- State Financing (Box 39, Folder 46-51)
- National Financing (Box 39, Folder 52-57)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project: LTV, Duquesne Light Economic Development Fund (Box 39, Folder 58)
- Morse Tool (Box 39, Folder 59)